crimsontrace.com 2019-05-13

# American Outdoor Brands

## Privacy Notice

### AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION

#### Website Privacy Notice and Policy

EFFECTIVE: November 30, 2018

This Privacy Notice and Policy ("this Policy") describes how AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION and its subsidiaries and corporate affiliates, ("we", "us", “our”, or "AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION") collect and use personal information when you use, access, or respond to our websites as well as any online applications; mobile applications; e-mail; telephone inquiries; sweepstakes, contest and rebate submissions; product and warranty registrations; newsletters; forums; posts; comments; surveys; and the like; and the websites and applications maintained and operated by our third-party contractors or service providers (collectively, the “Services”).

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Through your use of our Services we collect personal information, which is information that identifies you as an individual, relates to you as an identifiable individual, or that, along with other information, could identify you. We collect the following types of personal information:

#### _Information You Provide To Us_

We collect personal information from you when you use our Services. We do not require you to provide any personal information in order to navigate our websites. We collect information from you when (1) you provide it voluntarily to us in response to a request for such information, and (2) automatically by means which are part of the applications needed to provide the Services to you. For example, we may request your personal information, such as: your name, age (birthdate), gender, company name, mailing and billing addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, zip codes and credit card information. We may also collect other information that you submit in connection with our Services, including product reviews, sweepstakes or contest entries, consumer rebate submissions, product or warranty registration, and other similar information. Information obtained automatically through application usage consists primarily of anonymous usage statistics, but also includes first- and third-party cookies. For proper functionality of the Services, a minimum of anonymous usage data and first-party cookies are required to be collected.

#### _Information We Get From Third Parties_

We use third-party contractors or service providers to help us provide our Services. As part of these activities we obtain information collected by our third-party contractors or service providers such as: website or application visitor activity, eCommerce conversions, sweepstakes or contest participation, campaign tracking, consumer rebate submissions, product or warranty registration, and other similar information.

We may provide links to social media platforms such as Facebook and Instagram. These third-party applications may collect information about your IP address, and they may set cookies for the purposes these third-party contractors or service providers have described in their privacy policies. Your interaction with those applications is governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them, and not by this Policy.

#### _Information Collected Automatically_

We may, directly or indirectly (through a third party), collect information about you and your use of our Services whenever you use the Services. For example, we may collect information about your IP address, your user behavior (e.g., click activity), Services traffic statistics, operating system, and browser type. This data generally does not personally identify you and is automatically collected (as third-party cookies) when you use our Services. This anonymous information is helpful for marketing purposes and improving our Services

#### _Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies_

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser software on your computer’s hard drive or temporarily in your computer’s memory. We or our third-party providers place and store Internet cookies on your hard drive. Cookies can save any of the types of information noted above. Cookies enable us to personalize your viewing experience. When you revisit our website, we can recognize you by the cookie and customize your experience at this website accordingly. We, our service providers, or our third-party contractors may use technology such as cookies and web beacons/pixel tags to provide: eCommerce services within the application, advertising conversion analysis, marketing campaign analysis, user behavior and application usage analysis, user registration and authentication, and to provide a customized, more relevant user experience.

#### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We use your personal information to provide the Services to you, to improve our Services, and to protect our legal rights. We limit the collection of personal information to that which is relevant for these purposes. We will not store, access, transmit, retain or otherwise use personal information in any way that is incompatible with the purposes for which it has been collected or stored as described in this Policy without your consent.

We process your information for the following purposes as necessary to provide the Services to you and perform our contract with you:

  * **Facilitate your orders.**
  * **Communicate with you:** to communicate with you about our Services (including the notifications that are part of our Services), to send you account updates or other communications regarding your account or to inform you of any changes to our Services.
  * **Provide Customer Support:** to provide you support or other services you request. For example, we may need your information in order to provide technical support or answer questions about our Services.

We process your information for the following purposes as part of our legitimate interest in the improvement and marketing of our Services, and in the security of our Services. We apply appropriate safeguards to protect your information including as described here SECURITY, here CHOICES ABOUT YOUR INFORMATION and here RIGHTS OF RESIDENTS IN THE EU:

  * **Communicate about new features:** We send you notifications about new features or information available on our Services or that we feel might be of interest to you, such as product information, news, marketing and promotional materials, surveys, and the like. You can opt-out by following the opt-out instructions provided in our communications to you.
  * **To maintain and improve our Services:** We analyze how our users interact with our Services in order to maintain and improve our Services. We also use information that we collect to diagnose any problems with our Services.
  * **Benchmarking:** We aggregate your information in order to gain insights into our Services.

In our processing of your information, we also share your personal information to defend our rights and the rights of others, to efficiently maintain our business, and to comply with the law as described in this Policy.

#### HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION

We share your information with our service providers, among our subsidiaries and corporate affiliates, in connection with a corporate restructuring, to prevent harm, to comply with the law, and to protect our legal rights. The legal basis for this is our legitimate interest in providing our Services, complying with the law, and protecting our rights and those of others. We apply appropriate safeguards for this sharing of your information including as described below and in SECURITY, CHOICES ABOUT YOUR INFORMATION, and RIGHTS OF RESIDENTS IN THE EU.

  * **Service Providers:** We share information with third-party contractors and service providers that help us perform functions related to our Services and process your transactions, including, but not limited to conducting product reviews or surveys, administering sweepstakes or contests, processing consumer rebate submissions, processing product or warranty registrations, placing orders, delivering packages, analyzing and maintaining data, and other similar functions. These third-party contractors and service providers will only use your personal information for the purposes required to perform their functions.
  * **Marketing:** We may share your anonymous marketing information with Internet search engines (e.g., Google Analytics) and social media platforms (e.g., Facebook and Instagram) for re-marketing purposes. Corporate Structure: We would share information if we are involved or intend to be involved in a merger, acquisition, consolidation, change of control, or sale of all or a portion of our assets or in connection with bankruptcy or liquidation proceedings.
  * **To Prevent Harm:** We may share information if we believe it is necessary in order to detect, investigate, prevent, or take action against illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the rights, property, or personal safety of any person.
  * **To Protect Our Rights and As Required by Law:** We will share information where we are legally required to do so, such as in response to court orders or legal process, to exercise our legal rights, to defend against legal claims or demands, or to comply with the requirements of any mandatory applicable law. We will also share information as necessary to enforce the Terms and any other terms that you have agreed to, including to protect the rights, property, or safety of AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION, its users, or any other person, or the copyright-protected content of the Services.
  * **With Your Consent:** We will request your permission to use or share your personal information for a specific purpose that is not compatible with the purposes listed here. We will notify you and request consent before you provide the personal information or before the personal information you have already provided is shared for such purpose.

#### SECURITY

The security of your personal information is important to us. We maintain reasonable physical, technical, and administrative security measures to protect and limit access to your personal information. No method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage technology is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### CHOICES ABOUT YOUR INFORMATION

**Access, correct or delete your information:** You may use your account to access or correct the information you provided to us and which is associated with your account by contacting us by mail at American Outdoor Brands Corporation Legal Dept., 2100 Roosevelt Ave., Springfield, MA 01104, U.S.A., or by emailing us at dataprivacy@aob.com. Please include your name, mailing address and e-mail address when you contact us. You must describe the information that you want to access, remove, correct, or modify in sufficient detail to allow us to locate that information in our records. We may require you to verify your identity before allowing you to access, remove, correct, or modify your Personally Identifiable Information. Please note that a request to remove or modify information may prevent us from providing certain products or services to you. We will not remove or modify information associated with your prior purchase or registration of a product.

Even if you terminate your account, keep in mind that deletion of your personal information by our third-party contractors and service providers may not be immediate and that deleted personal information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time and as required by applicable laws and regulations. See: HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION. In the event that we refuse a request under rights of access, we will provide the individual with a reason as to why. Individuals residing in the EU also have the rights described in RIGHTS OF RESIDENTS IN THE EU.

**Do Not Track:** We take no action in response to “Do Not Track” requests received from user’s web browsing software.

**Advertising cookies:** To opt out of interest based advertising or to learn more about the use of this information by our service providers you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative website (http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) or the Digital Advertising Alliance website (http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), or if you are in the EU, the EDAA (http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). If you choose to opt out, we will place an “opt-out cookie” on your computer. The “opt-out cookie” is browser specific and device specific and only lasts until cookies are cleared from your browser or device. The opt-out cookie will not work for some cookies that are important to how our websites and mobile apps work (“essential cookies”). If the cookie is removed or deleted, if you upgrade your browser or if you visit us from a different computer, you will need to return to the applicable website to re-select your preferences.

**Cookies:** If you would like to opt out of accepting cookies altogether, you can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. Please note that certain functions of our websites may not function properly if your web browser does not accept cookies. If you choose to opt out, we will place an “opt-out cookie” on your computer. The “opt-out cookie” is browser specific and device specific and only lasts until cookies are cleared from your browser or device. The opt-out cookie will not work for some cookies that are important to how our websites and mobile apps work (“essential cookies”). If the cookie is removed or deleted, if you upgrade your browser or if you visit us from a different computer, you will need to return and update your preferences.

**Marketing:** If you do not want us to share your information for marketing purposes, or want additional information about our disclosures of certain categories of your information to third parties for marketing purposes, requests may be submitted by mail at American Outdoor Brands Corporation Legal Dept., 2100 Roosevelt Ave., Springfield, MA 01104, U.S.A., or by email at legal@aob.com.Within thirty (30) days of receiving such a request, your name will be removed off of our marketing list and/or we will provide a list of the categories of Personally Identifiable Information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made by a User no more than once per calendar year.

#### RIGHTS OF RESIDENTS OF THE EUROPEAN UNION (EU)

If EU data protection laws apply to the processing of your data, we will be the data controller and you would be entitled by law to access, correct, amend, or delete personal information about you that we hold. A list of these rights is below. Please note that these rights are not absolute and certain exemptions apply. To exercise these rights please contact us by mail at American Outdoor Brands Corporation Legal Dept., 2100 Roosevelt Ave., Springfield, MA 01104, U.S.A., or by email at legal@aob.com. For your protection, we may need to verify your identity before responding to your request, such as verifying that the email address from which you send the request matches your email address that we have on file. In the event that we refuse a request under rights of access, we will provide you a reason as to why.

  * **The right to access:** You have the right to ask us for copies of your personal information. This right has some exemptions, which means you may not always receive all the information we process. When making a request, please provide an accurate description of the data you want access to.
  * **The right to rectification:** You have the right to ask us to rectify information you think is inaccurate. You also have the right to ask us to complete information you think is incomplete.
  * **The right to erasure:** You have the right to ask us to erase your personal information in certain circumstances, including (i) when your personal information is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or processed or (ii) your information must be erased to comply with a legal obligation in EU Union or Member State law.
  * **The right to restrict processing:** You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your information in certain circumstances, including (i) when the accuracy of the information is brought into question or (ii) when we no longer need the information for purposes of the processing but you require such information for the establishment, exercise, or defense of a legal claim. See CHOICES ABOUT YOUR INFORMATION for some ways you can restrict processing.
  * **The right to object to processing:** You have the right to object to processing if we are able to process your information because the process is in our legitimate interests. See CHOICES ABOUT YOUR INFORMATION for some ways you can object to processing.
  * **The right to data portability:** This only applies to information you have given us. You have the right to ask that we transfer the information you gave us from one organization to another, or give it to you.
  * **The right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority.** A list of Supervisory Authorities is available here: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm> .

#### HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION

We will retain your personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes contained in this Policy and in accordance with our records retention policies. We retain your information for longer periods for specific purposes to the extent that we are obliged to do so in accordance with applicable laws and regulations and/or as necessary to protect our legal rights or for certain business requirements. For example, when we process your payments, we will retain this data for longer periods of time as required for tax or accounting purposes. More specifically, we would retain some data for longer periods of time for the following reasons:

  * **Security, fraud & abuse prevention:** i.e. to protect you, other people, and us from fraud, abuse, and unauthorized access.
  * **Financial record-keeping:** When you make a payment to us we are often required to retain this information for long periods of time for purposes of accounting, dispute resolution and compliance with tax, anti-money laundering, and other financial regulations.
  * **Complying with legal or regulatory requirements:** To meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, as required to enforce our terms of service, including investigation of potential violations.
  * **Direct communications with us:** If you have directly communicated with us, through a customer support channel, feedback form, or a bug report, we may retain reasonable records of those communications.

Even if you delete your account, keep in mind that the deletion by our third-party contractors and service providers may not be immediate and that the deleted information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time.

#### CROSS BORDER TRANSFERS OF INFORMATION

AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION may transfer your personal information to a jurisdiction outside the country where you reside, including processing personal information in the United States of America. Because not all jurisdictions may require the same levels of privacy protection as your jurisdiction of residence, your use of the Services constitutes your agreement to transfer your personal information. Even where AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION does make such transfers, the rights and obligations under this Policy will remain applicable to your personal information, except where prohibited by local law.

#### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Our websites and Services are not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 16 years. If we become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to delete such personal information without undue delay. The use of our Services for purchases is intended for persons eighteen (18) years of age and older.

#### THIRD PARTY WEBSITE LINKS

This Policy applies solely to our Services. Our Services may contain links to websites owned or operated by third parties. Your use of third-party websites is done at your own risk and subject to any terms and conditions of use, privacy policies, and other practices or procedures for such websites. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION is not responsible or liable for the content of or your use of any third-party websites that you may access through links on our Services.

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may update or modify this Policy from time to time. We will post the changes to this page and will indicate the date they go into effect. We encourage you to review our Policy to stay informed. If we make changes that materially affect your privacy rights we will notify you of the changes by posting a prominent notice on our website or using other methods that we select, such as sending you an email.

#### CONTACT US

Any questions or concerns about the interpretation or operation of this Policy or about what may or may not be done with regard to your information should be directed to: American Outdoor Brands Corporation, c/o Chief Compliance Officer, 2100 Roosevelt Avenue, Springfield, Massachusetts 01104, U.S.A.

## Terms of Use

### AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION

#### TERMS OF USE AGREEMENT AND DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY

EFFECTIVE: November 30, 2018

PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY. By accessing the Services (defined below), you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set forth below. These terms and conditions are subject to change without notice. These terms and conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION (defined below), and govern your use of the Services, superseding any prior agreements between you and AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION, relating to your use of the Services. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT, DO NOT ACCESS THE SERVICES.

Welcome to [aob.com](https://aob.com/). AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION and its subsidiaries and corporate affiliates ("we", "us", “our”, or "AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION") provide the information, data, documents, prices, applications, text, images, graphics, video, audio, and all other content (collectively “Content”) contained on [aob.com](https://aob.com/) and all other websites and pages, as well as in any online applications; mobile applications; e-mail; telephone communications; sweepstakes, contest and rebate submissions; product and warranty registrations; newsletters; forums; posts; comments; surveys; and the like that AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS maintains, operates, or disseminates; and the websites and applications maintained and operated by our third-party contractors or service providers (collectively, the “Services”) for informational purposes only. By accessing the Services, you, and any parties on whose behalf or for whose benefit you access, view, or otherwise use (collectively “use”) the Services, (collectively, "you" or "User"), agree to be legally bound by and comply with the terms and conditions contained within this Terms of Use Agreement and Disclaimer of Liability (the "Agreement"). This Agreement governs the use of the Services including all Content contained therein and limits the liability of AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION resulting from any use of such Content.

In addition, please review our Privacy Notice and Policy, which explains AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION’s collection and use of Personally Identifiable Information.

#### 1\. Acceptance.

Accessing or otherwise using the Services constitutes your acceptance of the terms and conditions of this Agreement and our Privacy Notice and Policy. You represent and warrant that you have the legal authority to accept this Agreement on behalf of yourself and any parties on whose behalf or for whose benefit you access or otherwise use the Services. The Services are not intended to be used by children under 16 years of age. No information should be submitted to or posted to the Services by Users under 16 years of age.

#### 2\. Permission to Use; Limitations; Termination.

AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION hereby grants User a limited, non-exclusive and revocable permission to use the Services subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement. Use of certain pages, sections, portions, or components (collectively “Pages”) of the Services may be subject to additional terms relating to privacy of personal information or other matters as may be provided in a separate warning, notice, policy, or agreement (collectively “agreements”). All such additional agreements are hereby incorporated into this Agreement. To the extent that such additional agreements provide for additional restrictions on your use of the Services or additional limitations of liability, such restrictions or additional limitations of liability shall be in addition to those provided under this Agreement. Your access to certain content or Pages may be restricted in which event use of such content or Pages is prohibited unless specific permission to access such content or Pages is explicitly granted by AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION. The Services may be used only for personal non-commercial informational purposes only, and you may not use the Services for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by this Agreement. You may not use the Services in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the Services or interfere with any other person’s use and enjoyment of the Services. The Services are intended to be used by residents of the United States, its territories, possessions and protectorates, and residents of Canada only. You agree to be bound by and to comply with this Agreement as it may be modified from time to time as set forth in this Agreement. You also agree to be bound by and to comply with all applicable government laws and regulations pertaining to your use of the Services and its contents. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION may cancel your permission to use all or any part of the Services at any time for any reason in the sole discretion of AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION. Your permission to use the Services shall automatically terminate in the event that you violate this Agreement. All provisions of this Agreement other than the permission to use the Services shall survive termination.

#### 3\. Third-Party Websites/Vendors.

The Services may contain advertisements for third-parties, information about third-parties, links to third-party websites or social media platforms, and/or information or content provided by third-parties. The owners and affiliates of such providers are referred to in this Agreement as "Third-Party Vendors." Such advertisements, information, content, and links do not and shall not be construed as approval or endorsement of such Third-Party Vendors or their websites or social media platforms or pages by AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION makes no representation concerning the lack of any viruses or other harmful components on any Third-Party Vendor website or social media platform or pages to which our Services link, and AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION shall have no liability resulting from your use of any such Third-Party Vendor website or social media platform or pages. If you choose to contact, visit the websites, social media platforms, or pages, or transact business with Third-Party Vendors, you do so at your own risk, and your use of their websites, social medial platforms, or pages is subject to any applicable rules and policies of such Third-Party Vendors, including any applicable terms of use agreements or privacy policies of such Third-Party Vendors. Third-Party Vendors have no authority to act on our behalf or to bind us, and we are not responsible for the actions of Third-Party Vendors. You shall be responsible for taking such steps, as you deem appropriate to evaluate Third-Party Vendors and their services and products and otherwise protect your interests. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION is not and shall not be construed to be a party to any transactions that may be entered into between you and Third-Party Vendors.

#### 4\. User Postings: User Input.

The Services may, from time to time, provide a bulletin board service, chat areas, news groups, forums, communities, personal pages, calendars, or other message or social media services as a convenience for Users. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION assumes no obligation to monitor the contents on the Services but reserves the right to refuse to accept and to remove any posting at any time. You agree not to post any information, content, or materials that violate intellectual property laws, that are obscene, pornographic, defamatory, violent, harassing, or that otherwise violate applicable laws or community standards, that solicit or promote any illegal activity, or that do not pertain to the specific subject matter of the social medium, all as determined by AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION in its sole and absolute discretion. You acknowledge and agree that by providing you with the ability to view and distribute User generated content on any social medium, AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION is merely acting as a passive conduit for such distribution and is not undertaking any obligation or liability relating to any content or activity on the social medium. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION reserves the right to block or remove communications or materials that it determines, in its sole discretion, to be (a) abusive, harassing, threatening, violent, defamatory, pornographic, or obscene; (b) fraudulent, deceptive, or misleading; (c) in violation of a copyright, trademark, or other intellectual property right of another; (d) in violation of any law or regulation; (e) advertisements or offers to sell or buy any goods or services; (f) surveys, contests, pyramid schemes, or chain letters; (g) viruses, corrupted files, spyware, harvesters, or any software, application, or program that is intended to spy upon or damage the operation of a computer or collect information about others; (h) offensive or otherwise unacceptable to AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION in its sole and absolute discretion.

You acknowledge that any information and materials posted on the Services are subject to use by AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION free of charge in connection with operating the Services and promoting our business without further notification to or permission by you. By posting information and/or materials to the Services or otherwise providing them to AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION, you: (i) grant AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION a world-wide, perpetual, irrevocable, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, non-exclusive, and unrestricted license to copy, reproduce, adapt, transmit, edit, modify, or otherwise use, publicly display, distribute, translate and create compilations and derivative works from, any and all such information and materials (in any format or media); and (ii) waive all moral rights in and to all such information and materials in favor of AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION. By posting any information and/or materials to the Services or otherwise providing them to AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION, you represent and warrant that such information and materials: i) are original to you and that you have obtained all necessary rights in and to such information and materials to post, upload, or otherwise submit it; ii) does not violate any law; and iii) complies with this Agreement.

In the event you believe that the Services contain any unlawful or inappropriate information or materials, you should notify AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION at the following address: AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION Legal Dept., 2100 Roosevelt Avenue, Springfield, MA 01102-2208, or by emailing us at legal@aob.com. Users under the age of majority in their jurisdiction of residence should not access or make any postings on the Services without parental permission and by making such postings represent that they have obtained such permission. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION assumes no obligation to investigate the existence of parental permission for access to or use of the Services. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION may establish additional or different policies and guidelines from time to time regarding posting information on the Services. All electronic mail or communications provided to AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION may be used by AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION for any purpose without compensation to the contributor, subject to AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION’s then existing privacy policy. You agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between you and AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION as a result of this Agreement or use of the Services. You represent that any information that you provide using the Services shall be true.

#### 5\. Security; Privacy.

AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION’s strives to maintain the security of information provided in connection with the Services but cannot guarantee the security of any such information, and to the maximum extent permitted by law, AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION shall not be responsible for any disclosure or compromise of User information . Further, you are responsible for maintaining the security of any passwords or other access keys provided to or selected by you for any restricted pages of the Services. We have no obligation to store or maintain any information provided by or on behalf of you. Any personal information we collect will be subject to our Privacy Notice and Policy as may be modified from time to time. For information about AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION’s privacy policy and practices, please see AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION’s Privacy Notice and Policy located on [aob.com](https://aob.com/).

#### 6\. Changes to the Services; Limitation of Availability.

At any time and for any reason in our sole discretion, we may modify or discontinue any aspect or feature of the Services, including content, pages, social media, functionality, hours of availability, pricing, registration requirements, the domain name addresses through which the Services are accessible, or the equipment needed for the use of the Services. The availability of the Services are subject to periodic downtime for maintenance and repairs and are subject to interruption due to causes beyond our reasonable control, including computer viruses, failure of telecommunication links, or failure of Internet infrastructure. You acknowledge and agree that we shall not be responsible for any interruptions of the availability of the Services.

#### 7\. Exclusive User Remedy; Typographical Errors.

n the event that you are dissatisfied with any aspect of the Services, your sole remedy shall be to discontinue use of the Services. The content of the Services may contain errors, omissions or typographical errors. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION shall not be liable for any such errors. In the event that a product, service, or price is listed incorrectly due to an inaccuracy, typographical error, or error in pricing information, AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION shall not be liable to you for any claim whatsoever arising from the inaccuracy and shall have the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed for product or service(s) listed at the incorrect price. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is canceled, AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION shall issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the incorrect price. The websites of the subsidiaries and corporate affiliates of AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION may also contain additional terms and conditions that apply to the products or services offered through those websites.

#### 8\. Disclaimer Of Warranties.

Although we strive to provide high-quality content on the Services, we do not guarantee or warrant the accuracy, completeness, suitability, availability, or timeliness of anything posted on the Services. Prices and availability of products are subject to change without notice. The Services should not be relied upon for personal, medical, legal, or financial information or decisions, and you should consult an appropriate professional for specific advice tailored to your situation. THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED "AS-IS" AND “AS AVAILABLE”. WITH ALL FAULTS, AND AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION DISCLAIMS TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW ALL WARRANTIES RELATING TO THE SERVICES, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR TITLE, WARRANTIES AGAINST INFRINGEMENT OR INTERFERENCE WITH ENJOYMENT, OR WARRANTIES ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE. BY WAY OF ILLUSTRATION WITHOUT LIMITATION, AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SERVICES WILL FULFILL ANY USER'S PARTICULAR REQUIREMENTS, THAT ACCESS TO THE SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE OR THAT ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THE SERVICES IS ACCURATE. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION DOES NOT MAKE ANY WARRANTY REGARDING INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM ANY HYPERLINKED THIRD-PARTY VENDOR.

COMMENTS OR OPINIONS EXPRESSED ON THE SERVICES ARE THOSE OF THE RESPECTIVE USERS ONLY. THE VIEWS EXPRESSED ON THE SERVICES AND IN USER CONTENT DO NOT NECESSARILY REPRESENT OR REFLECT THE VIEWS OF AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION. AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR, AND DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY IN RELATION TO, THE USER CONTENT POSTED, UPLOADED OR OTHERWISE SUBMITTED TO OR THROUGH THE SERVICES.

ANY PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES DESCRIBED ON THE SERVICES ARE OFFERED IN JURISDICTIONS WHERE THEY MAY BE LEGALLY OFFERED. THE INFORMATION ON THE SERIVCES IS NOT AN OFFER OR SOLICITATION BY ANYONE IN ANYONE IN ANY JURISDICTION IN WHICH AN OFFER OR SOLICITATION CANNOT LEGALLY BE MADE, OR TO ANY PERSON TO WHOM IT IS UNLAWFUL TO MAKE A SOLICITATION.

#### 9\. Disclaimer Of Liability.

TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION NOR ANY OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, LICENSORS, PARTNERS, MANAGERS, SHAREHOLDERS, DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES OR OTHER AGENTS SHALL HAVE ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY TO ANY USER OR ITS PRINCIPALS OR AGENTS FOR ANY DAMAGES, WHETHER GENERAL, SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL, INCLUDING ANY LOST PROFITS OR LOST SAVINGS, WHETHER OR NOT FORESEEABLE AND WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, COMMON LAW OR ANY OTHER THEORY OF LIABILITY, STATUTE OR REGULATION. USER EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGES AND AGREES THAT AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION IS PROVIDING ACCESS TO THE SERVICES IN RELIANCE ON THE DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT, AND FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGES AND AGREES THAT SUCH LIMITATIONS ARE REASONABLE. IN NO EVENT SHALL AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION'S LIABILITY TO USER EXCEED THE FEES ACTUALLY PAID BY USER FOR USE OF THE SERVICES.

#### 10\. Proprietary Rights; Restrictions.

You acknowledge and agree that the Services’ content, design, code, underlying technology and related items are proprietary to AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION (or our licensors and vendors if applicable) and protected by U.S., Canadian, and international copyright laws, trade secret laws, trademark laws and other laws. The posting of content on the Services by AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION or our subsidiaries and affiliates does not constitute a waiver of any right in such content. This Agreement does not provide you with any right or interest in our proprietary rights related to the Services or otherwise, and all such rights shall continue to be owned by AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION (or our licensors or vendors if applicable). Except to the extent express written permission is given to you by AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION, you shall not copy, reproduce or otherwise duplicate the Services or their content, in whole or in part, or access or attempt to access any of our systems, programs, data, code, underlying technology, or content that is not made available for public use, or use any content on the Services other than for their intended purpose. Permission is hereby given to you to view, print or download information on the Services that is made available by AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION for public viewing, printing or downloading, for your own personal, non-commercial, informational use and not for republication, distribution, sale, transfer, preparation of derivative works or other use. Placing links to our websites on other sites is prohibited absent AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION’s permission. Data mining, harvesting or similar collection of email addresses or other information on the Services is prohibited. The trademarks appearing on the Services are trademarks of AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION or others and may not be used without the express written permission of AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION or their respective owners. If you believe that any content or other aspects of the Services infringe upon your rights or the rights of others, you should provide notice to us at the following address: AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION Legal Dept., Intellectual Property Dept., 2100 Roosevelt Avenue, Springfield, MA 01102-2208, in which event we may elect to investigate the matter further.

#### 11\. Choice of Law and Forum; Attorneys' Fees; Indemnification.

For Users who are not an individual resident in the province of Quebec, this Agreement shall be governed exclusively by its terms and by the laws of the United States and the Commonwealth of Massachusetts as applied to contracts entered into in Massachusetts between Massachusetts residents without regard to the state's rules concerning choice of law. You hereby expressly consent and agree to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in Hampden County, Massachusetts with respect to any litigation arising out of or relating to this Agreement, provided that we may bring an action to enforce our rights in any forum having jurisdiction. In the event we are required to incur any attorneys’ fees, costs or other expenses in connection with enforcing or defending our rights under this Agreement, you shall reimburse us for such attorneys' fees, costs and expenses. User agrees to indemnify AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION against any and all claims, actions, costs and expenses, including attorneys' fees, arising from the User's use of the Services or breach of this Agreement.

#### 12\. Other Provisions.

In the event that any provision of this Agreement is held to be invalid or unenforceable, the remainder of this Agreement shall continue in full force and effect, and the provision held to be invalid or unenforceable shall be automatically amended to most closely approximate the original provision on terms that are valid and enforceable and the court or other adjudicating authority holding such provision invalid or unenforceable shall make such amendment accordingly. This Agreement shall control over any conflicting documents or information, including information on the Services. We may modify the terms of this Agreement from time to time by posting changes to this Agreement on [aob.com](https://aob.com/). No provision of this Agreement may be amended, modified or waived except as provided in the foregoing sentence. You agree to review this Agreement from time to time and comply with any changes. Any use of the Services after our posting of any such changes shall constitute your acceptance of this Agreement as modified. The terms of this Agreement constitute the mutual agreement of the parties and shall be construed neutrally and not for or against either party. Any rights not expressly granted to User in this Agreement are reserved by AMERICAN OUTDOOR BRANDS CORPORATION.
